ad2links.com 2017-08-19

# Ad 2 links

The term 'Ad2Links' or 'us' or 'we' refers to the owner of the website 'Ad2links.com'. The term 'you' refers to the user or viewer of our website. The term 'Content' refers to the website you are using in conjunction with the Service.

We at Ad2links.com respect the privacy of our visitors and are committed to preserving your online safety by preserving your privacy at anytime you visit or communicate with our site. Our privacy policy has been provided and reviewed by the solicitors at Legal Centre who specialise in online internet contracts.

Our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy offers you a thorough explanation regarding your personal data provided to us or any data we may collect from you.

This Privacy Policy is updated from time to time; therefore, it should be reviewed occasionally.

When you look at the Ad2links.com web site, our counter records the following information:

This information is ONLY used for statistical purposes. If at any stage you provide us with your email address either as part of a message or by registering, we will only use your email address for the purposes for which it was provided. We will not subscribe your email address to any mailing list without your consent.   
We respect your privacy. Your information is confidential and will not be sold or shared with other companies or individuals.   
External sites that are linked to or from the Ad2links.com site are not under our control or responsibility and you are advised to review their privacy statement.

Disclaimer :  
This site is provided without warranty of any kind. There are no guarantees that it will be available at any given time, and no guarantees that this site or service will not be subject to interruptions. All direct or indirect risk related to use of this site is borne entirely by you, the user.

We reserve the right to amend or change these policies, terms and conditions at any time and without prior notice.
